BUDOGAOKA BANK
GREAT YEAR-END LOTTERY
Please accept our congratulations
on this momentous occasion.
It is very, very close to expiring,
but there is no question,
this is the third-place ticket
worth five million yen.
Now, then… If I may…
This is a promissory note
for the award of five million yen.
MORIOH STATION BRANCH
Please allow us three days
to process
before collecting your cash reward.
PROMISSORY NOTE
BUDOGAOKA BANK
MORIOH STATION BRANCH
TOTAL 5,000,000 YEN
PLEASE PAY THE AMOUNT STATED
ABOVE IN EXCHANGE FOR
THIS PROMISSORY NOTE.
One, ten, hundred, thousand…
It's got six zeros…
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
EPISODE 19
SHIGECHI'S HARVEST, PART 2
Now, there is something
I would like to ask you…
RECEPTION
From which store did you sirs
procure this winning ticket?
Sniff, sniff.
W-Which store?
Now why would you wanna know that?
It's a simple formality.
Damn dim-witted hoodlums.
You won five million yen? Bullshit.
This quick-witted teller
smells foul play.
Or perhaps
I am sensing some resistance
to answering my question?
W-Well, of course we bought it
in Morioh.
Oh? How very peculiar…
Not a single store
in Morioh sells lottery tickets.
O-Oh, right…
It must've been when
we went to S City.
We bought so much stuff,
it must've just slipped my mind…
I-I-I-I-I-It was so long ago…
I just noticed
something else peculiar…
On the reverse side of the ticket,
you will find spaces
for the ticket holder's
name and telephone number…
ICHIRO MORISHITA
Ichiro Morishita…
The name written here
doesn't match any of yours.
N-Name?!
Phone number?!
That was written on the back?!
E-Er…
Well, well, well, well,
this is peculiar.
This is your lottery ticket,
isn't it?
Oh, yeah! Now I remember!
I used it to write down
my friend's number!
Oh! Is that so?
Then whaddya say we give
Mr. Ichiro Morishita a call?
All lottery tickets are traceable
to their point of purchase
with their serial numbers.
If Mr. Ichiro Morishita
indeed purchased a lottery ticket
and can remember precisely
where he bought it,
we will then be obliged
to confirm his signature…
My, to whom does
this mysterious ticket belong?
Depending on what we learn,
we may have to
turn it over to the police.
The police?!
Hello? Morishita speaking.
Hello, this is Budogaoka Bank.
And I'm calling to inquire whether
a Mr. Ichiro Morishita
purchased a Great Year-End
Lottery ticket.
Yeah, I'm Ichiro Morishita.
I bought one.
In fact, I'm sure I bought one.
Yes! I got you, you pathetic brats!
I knew it, I still got it!
As if god in heaven would
bestow the winning ticket
on money-grubbing goons like you!
MORI
So you did!
You bought a lottery ticket.
Yeah, I did.
MORISHITA ICHIRO
I must've bought ten of 'em,
but they were all duds.
KINOSHITA ICHIRO
I'm returning only portions
of his writing
to their original forms…
Well I'm pleased to inform you,
Mr. Kinoshita,
your lottery ticket…
Kinoshita? My name's Morishita.
Huh? But it was
the character for "Mori"!
What? I just don't get it…
Your phone number is 1771 -1281,
correct, Mr. Kinoshita?
I told you, pinhead,
my name's not Kinoshita!
It's Morishita!
Why're you wasting
my time with this baloney?
I threw those damn things away
Sell me a goddammed winner
next time…
I'm sorry for the inconvenience…
Wait right there, boys!
The number you have reached
is no longer in service.
Please check the number
and dial again…
That good enough?
Please accept my deepest apologies.
Yay! I got my money!
My hard-won five million yen!
Hey, you promised.
Half would go to us, Shigechi!
Did I say that?
You're pulling that shit again?!
Hey, Josuke! What are you doing?!
You're not gonna let him
get away with it again, are you?
No… He's not getting off
scot-free this time!
No more Mr. Nice guy!
That's the spirit, Josuke!
I knew you wouldn't back down!
Who in their right mind would?!
Not in the mood to split the money
three ways anymore, eh, Shigechi?
That's just not gonna fly,
not with that kind of money.
Here.
This should be plenty for you guys.
It's not like you guys
did anything.
Think of that as a little
pity payment from your friend.
CRUSH
Why, you—
Hey, Okuyasu!
Hand it over, jerk-off!
You promised us half,
and half is what we're gonna get!
Serves you right, greedy bastard!
You always let your fists
do the talking. Control yourself.
When words don't work,
a little manhandling
always does the trick!
Are you hurt?
Okuyasu shouldn't have hit you.
Shigechi,
let's do this the easy way.
We're gonna hold onto
the promissory note
for the five million.
When we cash it in three days,
we'll split it, as promised,
half and half.
I'm so over that asshole.
No way in hell
I'm hanging with him anymore.
But you know,
we were the ones trying to exploit
the poor bastard for pocket money.
Guess we have a lot
to be sorry about.
You moron.
Huh?
Well, I see things
in a different way.
He got his hands on that
five million only because of us.
He'd be lucky to get
a few tens of thousands on his own.
He's walking away with 2.5 million.
2.5 million!
Yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes, yes, yes!
It stays with me.
It stays with me!
I heard everything, sneaky bastard!
I won't give you guys a single yen!
We got that five million
because of Harvest!
You're nothing compared
to my Harvest!
Wanna see proof?
You wanna see some hard proof?
I'll show you!
Ow!
- Bastard!
- No! Our five million yen IOU!
You're playing with
the wrong Stand users, dipshit!
Keep chasing me,
and I'll kill you.
Shigechi…
This fool says he's gonna kill us.
If you sic your Stand on us,
then prepare to meet your maker!
W-Wait, Josuke…
What's wrong?
I've got this weird feeling…
M-My legs…
they itch like a son of a bitch…
Itch? At a time like this?
It itches so bad!
My whole body itches!
Wh-What the hell is happening?!
Roll up your pants, Okuyasu! Hurry!
What?!
They got inside my pants!
I-It's no use!
Knocking off two or three of 'em
won't hurt him at all!
Dammit!
He's getting away!
He's starting to
really piss me off.
This guy has been pissing me off
the whole time!
Come to papa, five million!
He just made mortal enemies
of the hard-as-nails
Okuyasu-Josuke fighting duo!
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
Damn him!
No one makes a fool out of Okuyasu!
I'll beat you into a bloody pulp!
Well, now we know
he's a greedy bastard
and a complete idiot.
Blasted butterball!
I'd think twice about
trying to outrun us with that body!
See, told ya so, dumb-ass!
H-He's using Harvest underneath him
like a tank's caterpillar track,
or some kind of bucket relay!
Shit… This guy's insane fast!
He's not the brightest bulb
in the box,
but he's actually kinda clever.
It's like he comes up with
this crap by instinct.
Damn! We lost him!
Just hold your horses.
All we gotta do is…
pull the same trick
and have our Stands
do all the heavy lifting!
I get it!
My five million…
You really think you can
get away from us, Shigechi?
Bring it, blimp!
I'm gonna pop each and every one
of your little Harvest underlings!
My Harvest is amazing.
It can collect anything!
Even the kind of screws
that hold pipes together.
Bolts too!
I think you're forgetting about
the amazingness of
my Shining Diamond!
Well, hello.
I'm madder than hell,
but I'm still willing
to forgive you.
As long as I get
a few good last hits in!
Come on, give us that IOU,
Shigechi.
I told you…
Keep chasing me,
and I'll kill you.
W-What?
My hands…
That hurt…
I can't get up! Okuyasu, watch out!
He's up to something!
O-Okuyasu, you too?
Still can't figure it out?
You guys are drunk!
A-Alcohol?!
LIQUOR
My harvest can get their hands
on anything!
It carried some booze
all the way from the liquor store,
then injected it into your bodies!
Directly into your veins, in fact!
W-What?!
You bastard!
When alcohol's injected
into the veins,
it doesn't take much
to get shit-faced!
C-Come to think of it,
alcohol can be used as
an anesthetic…
Th-That bastard…
He isn't a total idiot,
after all…
No, it must be instinct.
I-I'm gonna murder him!
No way is a little tipsiness
gonna bring me down!
M-My eye!
Josuke, hurry, fix it quick!
W-Wait, Okuyasu!
If I remember correctly,
you guys called me unreasonable
and a whole bunch of other things,
didn't you?
I'll show you what happens
when you underestimate me!
D-Damn it!
So I guess that means you forgot
all about breaking your promise?
That's it… I'm this close!
Push me more, and I can't
guarantee what'll happen!
That's enough lip out of you,
Josuke!
You've got a sad excuse of a Stand!
You guys's powers are shit!
Try making demands after
you've got half of Harvest's power!
Josuke, close your eyes!
Josuke!
So close!
There's no point
in closing your eyes.
Harvest can get anything!
He'll just tear off your eyelid
and gorge out your eye!
We get it, Shigechi, stop!
Forgive us! We were wrong.
Oh? Is that an apology?
Damn it, you little punk!
Oh? Okuyasu, it seems Josuke
doesn't share your sentiment.
I-I'll make him share my sentiment!
We'll give you this!
It's the 10,000 yen you gave me
and everything else I have.
Take it as our penitence.
Who's gonna fix my eye
if Josuke is offed?
O-Okuyasu…
Oh, yeah! That's right!
I felt so bad for you guys,
I blessed you with over 10,000 yen!
Here, take it,
just have mercy on us.
Brilliant, Okuyasu!
Like catching a tanuki
with a little bait,
you'll lure him in
with some cash and then bam!
I'm right there with you, buddy!
Okuyasu, that newfound obedience
leaves a good impression.
There, there.
Hey, wait a sec.
Okuyasu, you wouldn't be trying to
lure me in with cash
so you can attack me
with your Stand, would you?
Ah! So you are!
Did you really think
I'd fall for that?
You really thought
I was that stupid?
No more pity!
Fine by us,
we don't need your pity.
But it's too late.
Didn't realize you're already
well within The Hand's range?
I'll claw away mid-air
and make it
teleport!
We got back what's rightfully ours.
Got it back?
W-What are you talking about?
I'll just take it back…
You just don't get it,
do you, Shigechi?
Your chance of winning
just expired.
My five million!
What are you doing?!
I don't get it! I don't get it!
Stop!
Why would you do that?!
I don't get it! I don't get it!
That's five million yen!
You could try to hurt us…
even kill us.
But, you see,
the only way of fixing this thing
is with Shining Diamond…
You can't win this fight.
Oh… I-I see! I get it!
And with this, you can
kiss any hope of victory good bye.
H-Huh? I don't get it!
I don't get it!
I don't get it! I don't get it!
What are you doing?!
Get every last scrap, Harvest!
Guess I gotta spell it out
for you again…
Sending Harvest after the pieces
was the nail in the coffin.
So who's gonna protect you
from these two drunks now?
Oh, I get it…
SMASH
We did it.
So, old buddy, old pal…
I think we're due for
a little study time.
The little scraps are
picked up by Harvest, and…
the little scraps are
put back together by…?
Well?
I'm waiting…
Who can put the scraps
back together with Shining Diamond?
J-Josuke…
WHACK
M-Mr. Josuke, sir!
Damn straight, Mr. Josuke, sir.
And the one who recovered
that IOU from you is…
Say his name.
O-Okuyasu…
Mr. Okuyasu!
That's it. Good boy.
All right,
it's time for mathematics.
How do we split the five million?
How do we split it
so that everyone is happy?
I'm happy with half…
Half?
You do know there are
three of us here, right?
Half doesn't seem at all
weird to you?
That's just not very good math.
Anyone home?
I-It'd be a third…
Th-That's right…
I'd have only been able
to gather stuff.
I-I was wrong.
We all found this lottery ticket.
We wouldn't have ever gotten it
without the three of us
working together.
I…
I can see now.
My greed kept me
from seeing the truth.
We split everything fair and square
so everyone is happy.
BAM
Yes!
Real cash!
I-It's five million yen!
Rest assured your money
would be safe with Budogaoka Bank.
Of course!
We finally did it!
I must be dreaming!
Wait…
Weren't we gonna
split everything up
so everyone would be happy?
Huh? That's strange.
If we're gonna split it up
fair and square,
don't we have to
include our Stands?
Harvest is made up of
about 500 Stands,
so we should split it
500 to 1 and 1.
You don't disagree, do you?
You little bastard!
Trying to haggle again?
You still don't know
when to stop, do you, idiot!
Okay, one third is fine!
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
- CURRENT SAVINGS - 1,666,666 YEN
For some, that is far too much
for a high school freshman
to have, but…
To be continued!
EPISODE 20
YUKAKO YAMAGISHI
DREAMS OF CINDERELLA